ILGWU. Susan Cowell papers, 5780/097
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Labor rights and trade, 1987-1995 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Mandela, June, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Maquiladoras, Mexico, 1989-1991 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Dick Morris Consultants, miscellaneous, 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Morris, proposal for imports, 1983-1987 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Dick Morris, survey results, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- New York City, North American Free Trade Agreement (NAFTA), 1992-1993 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- New York State, AFL-CIO endorsements, 1986-1988 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Nicaragua elections, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- North American Free Trade Agreement (NAFTA) Campaign, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 21)
- North American Free Trade Agreement (NAFTA), fast track, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 22)
- Organizing Free Trade Zones, 1990-1992 (Box 22, Folder 23)
- Override follow-up, failure to override President's veto of the Textile and Apparel Trade Enforcement Act, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 24)
- Thailand Fire, 1993-1995 (Box 22, Folder 25)
- Third World labor conditions, 1986-1999 (Box 22, Folder 26)
- Trade analysis (Box 22, Folder 27)
- Trade analysis (Box 22, Folder 28)
- Trade bill, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 29)
- Trade bill, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 30)
- Trade bill, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 31)
- Veto Override Campaign, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 32)
- Walmart expose, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 33)
- Washington Post advertisement, November, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 34)
- Wool Tariff, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 35)
- Chaikin, Chick (President of ILGWU, 1975-1986), 1991 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Dubrow, Evelyn, dinner, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Dubrow, Evelyn, dinner, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Dubrow, Evelyn, internship, 1986-1998 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- General Advisory Council, creation, 1983-1985 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- General Advisory Council, meetings, 1985-1995 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- General Advisory Council, recommendations and appointments, 1984-1985 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- General Advisory Council, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Hart Survey, for membership attitudes toward union-sponsored benefits, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- ILGWU, Associate Membership Benefits for Executives, 1986-1992 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- ILGWU, Associate Membership bylaws, 1988-1995 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- ILGWU, Associate Membership, central states, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- ILGWU, Associate Program, 1987-1994 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- ILGWU, "Future of Work," meeting, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- ILGWU, general, 1983-1997 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- ILGWU, membership, 1985-1987 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- ILGWU, parental policies, 1987-1996 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- ILGWU, scholarship, 1993-1995 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- Local 10, 1994-1995 (Box 23, Folder 19)
- Merger, clippings, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Merger, clippings, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Merger Convention, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 22)
- New Jersey Garment Industry, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 23)
- Public Art Commission, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 24)
- Tenement Museum, 1992-1995 (Box 23, Folder 25)
- Wool Fabric, June, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Garment Center Zoning--Guiliani, 1994-1999 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Garment Center Zoning, 1997-1999 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- New York City Policy, Garment Industry, 1990-1993 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- New York Garment Industry, 1982-1993 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- UNITE, NYC Agenda, 2000-2002 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Real Estate pressure, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Behind the Label retailers, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- UNITE sweatshop campaign, 1995-1998 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Federal sweatshops, 1994-2001 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- AFL-CIO sweatshop rally, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Smithsonian, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- New York State, sweatshop, 1994-1999 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Sweatshop Summit, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Monitoring, sweatshops, 1996-1999 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Verification proposal, alternative monitoring program, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Corporate responsibility, 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Retailers, 1995-2000 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Living wage, 1998-2000 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Partnership/coalition, 1995-1997 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Reich/Citizens' Committee Against Sweatshops, 1997-1998 (Box 24, Folder 21)
- UNITE, Canada, 1997-2000 (Box 24, Folder 22)
- Sweatshop facts (Box 24, Folder 23)
- Labeling, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 24)
- China report, 1997-1998 (Box 24, Folder 25)
- GAP Campaign/Kernaghan, Charles (Executive Director of National Labor Committee), 1995 (Box 24, Folder 26)
- National Labor Committee, 1997-2000 (Box 24, Folder 27)
- European Clean Clothes Campaign, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 28)
- Codes of Conduct, 1992-1999 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Sunset Park Demonstration (fair wages and work conditions), 1995 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Post Apparel Industry Partnership (AIP) response, 1998-2000 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Anti-Sweatshop Retreat, November, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Worker Rights Consortium, 2000-2001 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- White House Partnership, 1997-1999 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- UNITE! A Brief History of the ILGWU, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Employer Contributed Benefit Fund Report to 42nd Convention, June, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- 42nd Convention, June 23-30, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- 41st Convention, June 12-19, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- 40th Convention, June, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- 39th Convention, June 3-6, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Russian document, March 14, 1923 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Research, September, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Research, January 30, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Research, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Local 23-25, Child Care Research, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Financial documents and general funds, 1989-1994 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- ILGWU, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Child Care Study of the New York City Garment Industry, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Garment Industry Day Care Center of Chinatown (New York City), 1984-1989 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- Garment Industry Day Care Center of Chinatown (New York City), 1990-1995 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Cowell, Susan, convention planner, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Cowell, Susan, convention planner, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 18)
- Hart Survey, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 19)
- UNITE! Against Sweatshops, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 20)
- Champagne pour l'avenir, Canada, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 21)
- The Face of Change: UNITE! (Box 26, Folder 22)
- Newman, Pauline, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 23)
- ILGWU, Union Health Care Center: 75 Years of Service, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 24)
- Child Care Study of the New York City Garment Industry, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- '95 Convention, 1994-1995 (Box 26, Folder 26)
- Convention speakers, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 27)
- Guest awardees, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 28)
- Name, logo, 1995-1996 (Box 26, Folder 29)
- Merger, press, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 30)
- Merger, education, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Convention video, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Child Care '95, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Convention Committee '95, 1992-1995 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Program '95, 1992-1995 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- ACTWU Merger, 1993-1995 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Merger documents, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 7)